http://www.tacocabana.com/privacy

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyShhhh. Privacy Please!
Taco Cabana Privacy Policy
Last updated: June 17, 2020
Welcome to the Texas Taco Cabana, L.P. ("Taco Cabana") website. Below you will find our Privacy Policy describing the information practices of Taco Cabana and, as applicable, our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and related entities such as Fiesta Restaurant Group, Inc. (“Fiesta”) and Pollo Operations, Inc. (collectively the “Affiliates”), (Taco Cabana and its Affiliates are referred to as “we”, “us”, or “our"). This Privacy Policy covers the information that we collect about you on our Sites (as defined below), how we use and share that information, and your choices regarding our collection and use.
Our goal is to protect your privacy and the information that you submit to us through the Internet. We operate our Sites from Fiesta’s corporate office in Dallas, Texas in the United States. All matters pertaining to our Sites are governed and interpreted under the laws of the State of Texas, United States.
By accessing our Sites, you indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your agreement to the Terms of Use posted on our Sites. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at contact@frgi.com.
Our Sites are not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13) and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) on our Sites. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen (13) on our Sites, we will delete the information from our records.
Special Assistance
Special assistance is available for persons with disabilities. If you need assistance accessing our Sites, please call us toll free at 1-888-778-7696
Information Collected
We and our third-party service providers collect information about you from a variety of sources, including information you provide directly to us, and information we collect about you when you interact with us. For example, we and our third-party service providers collect information both directly and indirectly from you when you:
· access or use our websites, our mobile applications, our loyalty program, our Promotions (defined below), and any other website or application where this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, our "Sites");
· order and/or purchase any of our products or services;
· contact or communicate with us;
· create an account with us;
· request information from us;
· register for any event and/or participate in any event, contest, surveys, or other promotion that we may offer from time to time (collectively, “Promotions”);
· register for, access or use our loyalty program;
· begin or complete the application process for a franchise opportunity, or for employment by us;
· access or use our pages or accounts on any third-party social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram (“Social Media Pages”);
· sign-up for communications from us; and/or provide or submit comments, suggestions, or other content or input to us.
We may combine any of the information collected about you for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
When you submit an order online, your information will be collected and processed by our online ordering service provider, Mobo Systems, Inc. d/b/a Olo and will be subject to their privacy policy located at https://olo.tacocabana.com/help/privacypolicy.
When you order catering, order our food through third party delivery service providers, or access our loyalty program, your information will be collected and processed by third party providers subject to their respective privacy policies on their respective websites.
Personal Information
We and our third-party service providers collect information that identifies you personally provided by you or on your behalf, which information may include your: name, address, telephone numbers (including mobile numbers), email addresses, date of birth and/or age, demographic information, and/or financial information (e.g., credit and debit card numbers) (“Personal Information”). We do not require you to provide any information related to your racial origin, religious beliefs, or sexual orientation.
Transaction Data
We and our third-party service providers may also collect information, including Personal Information, relating to your purchases from our restaurants or our Franchisees or Licensees, payment method, the date and time of the transaction, items purchased, and the purchase price ("Transaction Data").
Information Collected Automatically
We and our third-party service providers use tracking technologies to automatically collect certain information from you. The following are examples of information we may collect with these technologies:
· your IP address;
· browser type and operating system;
· mobile device type;
· pages you view within our Sites;
· websites you visited before coming to our Site;
· emails from us that you open and/or forward; and/or
· offers or links from us to which you connect.
We use this information to personalize your online experience and for marketing purposes.
Traffic Data. Our Sites automatically track and collect your IP address, domain server, type of computer, and type of web browser (collectively, “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data does not typically include Personal Information, but rather is anonymous information that is helpful for our marketing purposes for improving your experience on our Sites.
Cookies. We also use cookies, which are small text files that are stored on a user’s computer and allow websites to remember information about users (“Cookies”). We use Cookies to monitor how our Sites are used and to help personalize your online experience. Most browsers automatically accept Cookies. You have the choice to set your browser to accept or reject Cookies. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your Cookie preferences.
Web Beacons. Certain pages on our Sites and Social Media Pages may contain web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, and clear GIFs), which are small bits of code embedded in pages or images on our Sites and Social Media Pages (“Web Beacons”). We may also include Web Beacons in e-mails we send to you to learn if messages have been opened, acted on, or forwarded. You can disable the ability of Web Beacons to capture such information. Please refer to the "Help" menu of your browser to learn more about Web Beacons and your ability to disable them.
Other Technologies. We and our third-party service providers may also utilize other tracking technologies. For example, if permitted by applicable law, we may collect "referrers" and various environmental variables. A "referrer" is information the web browser passes along to our or our third-party service provider web servers, which refers to the URL from which you accessed our Site. Environmental variables may include, among other things, the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed our Site or Social Media Page, the type of web browsers and operating system or platform used, the Internet address of the website you left to visit our Site or Social Media Page, the names of the web pages you visit, and the Internet address of the website you visit next. These environmental variables are collected by most websites, and can be used to optimize your online experience.
We treat information automatically collected as non-personally identifying information, except to the extent required by applicable law. Such information may be combined with your Personal Information so that we can make our Sites and communications more personalized for you. To the extent that information automatically collected is combined with Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.
Mobile Applications
In addition to the information described above, we and our third-party service providers may collect additional information when you utilize any of our mobile applications, including the type of mobile device you use, the temporary or persistent unique device identifiers, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use our mobile applications.
If you utilize any of the location-based services in our mobile applications, we and our third-party service providers may collect, use, and share location data, including the real-time geographic location of your device. We use such information to provide and improve location-based products and services. You may opt-out from further allowing us to have access to your location data by adjusting the permissions in your mobile device.
Information Use
We use your information that we collect, including Personal Information, for a variety of business purposes, including:
· providing our products and services to you;
· processing payments;
· communicating with you regarding our restaurants, products, services, events, Promotions, and other offers;
· making our Sites and communications tailored to your interests;
· creating and managing your accounts with us;
· administering our Promotions and other offers;
· tailoring our products, services, Sites, and advertisements to your interests;
· responding to your inquiries, comments, stories, or postings;
· improving and customizing our products, services, and Sites according to your individual interests;
· for internal operations such as enhancing our product and service offerings, marketing efforts, and to conduct research and analysis;
· developing new products, services, and Promotions;
· for marketing purposes;
· to enforce our Terms of Use ; and/or
· to protect the security and integrity of our business and our Sites.
We may use your information to match it with other data sources in order to enhance our records, such as appending additional information to your profile. We may use data and service providers to identify different devices that you use to match all of those devices to you, such as desktop computer, laptop and smartphone. Such matching enables us to improve our advertising and understand how you use the Sites.
Third Party Disclosures
We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes. We may share Personal Information provided by our visitors to this Site with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are restricted from using or disclosing such Personal Information except in anonymized form or as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through our Sites in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Facebook Sign In
You may create an account or sign into your account on the Sites by clicking on “Sign in with Facebook” and then entering your Facebook login credentials. In this case, we may receive information from Facebook to make it easier for you to create an account on the Sites. Once you register on the Sites and connect with Facebook, information you post or provide access to may be publicly displayed on the Sites or by Facebook. Both Pollo Tropical and Facebook may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Sites and Facebook’s services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of Facebook, and you are encouraged to read their policies and set your privacy preferences appropriately.
Employment Applicants
If you complete an application for employment with us, or request information regarding such opportunities, we collect Personal Information that you provide in connection with your request for information and/or to evaluate your application for employment. By applying to become an employee you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information in this manner.
Franchise Applicants
If you complete an application to become a franchisee, or request information regarding such opportunities, we collect Personal Information that you provide in connection with your request for information and/or to evaluate your application to become a franchisee. By applying to become a franchisee you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information in this manner.
Your Choices
Access and Deletion Requests
We provide you with the opportunity to update and/or delete certain information that we collect from you, such as profile and account information. For any such requests, you may contact us via the Contact Information provided at the end of this policy. We will make good faith efforts to comply with such update and/or deletion requests as soon as possible, but cannot guarantee complete update or removal of the requested information from our databases.
Communications
We also provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used or disclosed for certain purposes. You may update your choices by contacting us via the Contact Information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy, or following instructions provided in communications sent to you. Because we plan our communications in advance, please allow some time for your request to become effective. If you opt-out but continue to receive communications, please contact us so that we can address the issue.
Interest-Based Advertising
We may ourselves or with third parties, use non-identifying information to deliver interest-based advertisements to you based upon your online activities and other information. The online advertising industry provides a service through which you may opt-out of receiving interest-based advertising from certain third party providers that participate in self-regulatory programs. Some of the third parties that provide us such advertising services comply with, and we comply with, the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising set forth by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You can opt-out of targeted advertising from certain providers at www.aboutads.info/consumers. For mobile devises, you may also download and set your preferences on the App Choices mobile application(s) available in Google Play or the Apple App stores to limit ads in certain apps or may set the limit ad tracking setting or to reset the advertising identifier on your iOS and Android device.
Some of these third parties may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, see www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.
Even if you opt out, note that you will continue to see generic advertising that is not tailored to your interests and activities. Whether you use our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted out on your desktop browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device. We do not respond to or honor “do not track” (a/k/a DNT) signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.
Analytics
We may use third-party analytics services such as Google Analytics on our Sites to analyze your use of the Sites, and our performance and delivery of our products, services and advertising. To learn how to opt out of Google Analytics services, you can go to https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout for more information.
Information Security
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the personal information you provide on our Sites. We use secure socket layer (SSL) technology to help keep the personal information you provide on our Sites secure. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit card number, we use at least industry standard methods to protect that information. We also request that our third-party service providers use commercially reasonable security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access or use. However, no method of electronically transmitting or storing data is ever completely secure, and therefore, we cannot guarantee that your information will never be accessed, used, or disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
Linked Sites
Our Sites and communications may contain links to other third-party websites (“Linked Sites”). We are not responsible for the privacy practices, policies, or content of any Linked Sites, even if you link to them from our Sites or communications. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Linked Sites. We have no control over the collection or use of information, including Personal Information, on any Linked Site. We encourage you to read and understand the privacy policies of any Linked Sites that you visit.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
This Privacy Statement may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you. Your continued use of our Sites and/or provision of your information following any such changes constitute your unconditional agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy each time you use or access our Sites.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your Personal Information, please contact us by e-mail at contact@frgi.com.
